infoaxe.net 2010-01-05

# Infoaxe Privacy Policy

At Infoaxe, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. We have created this policy to demonstrate our commitment to you and to help you understand it. 

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the Infoaxe website and services, post a link to the Infoaxe website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or in anonymous form, with third parties. 

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. 

Infoaxe reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with Infoaxe, you can send an e-mail, in English please, to support@infoaxe.com.
